{
    "subject": "resource/Sakyo_Komatsu",
    "predicate": "ontology/nationality",
    "object": "resource/Japanese_people",
    "human_readable": "Sakyo Komatsu's nationality is Japanese people.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9378218054771423,
            "question": "Is Sakyo Komatsu Japanese?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9363765716552734,
            "question": "What is Sakyo Komatsu's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8886223435401917,
            "question": "What nationality defines Sakyo Komatsu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7361415028572083,
            "question": "To which country does Sakyo Komatsu belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6465515494346619,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Sakyo Komatsu's nationality and his writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5536314249038696,
            "question": "Where is Sakyo Komatsu from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46030208468437195,
            "question": "Who are some other famous Japanese people?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3009188175201416,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Sakyo Komatsu's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2325713336467743,
            "question": "What is Japanese culture known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.035711560398340225,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of Japanese literature?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sakyo Komatsu's nationality is Japanese people.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8413_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Japanese culture known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8413_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Sakyo Komatsu's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8413_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some other famous Japanese people?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8413_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8413_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8413_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8413_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8413_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8413_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8413_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8413_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8413_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8413_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8413_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n`{\"output\": \"yes\"}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Sakyo Komatsu, confirming that he was a Japanese science fiction writer. This supports the statement that his nationality is Japanese."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}